(Leonard:)All right.
- And what is your name?
- Angela.
(Raj:)Oh, derived from the word
"angel." Appropriate.
(Angela:)You're cute.
(Sheldon:)I'd like to buy a scone.
(Server:)Oh, I'm sorry, we're out.
(Server:)We have muffins.
(Sheldon:)They sound delicious,
(Sheldon:)but this money
is earmarked for scones.
(Penny:)What are
you doing?!
(Raj(taking his shirt off):)Oh, just getting comfortable.
(Raj(taking his shirt off):)So how long have you
lived in Los Angeles?
(Scene:)I...
(Sheldon:)They were out of scones.
(Raj(removing his trousers):)Sheldon, I'm talking to someone.
(Raj(removing his trousers):)You're being rude.
(Raj(removing his trousers):)I'll bet you're an actress.
(Raj(removing his trousers):)If not, you should be.
(Raj(removing his trousers):)You have a very expressive face.
(Angela:)Oh, my God.
(Raj:)Wait, where are you going?
(Raj:)We were doing so well.
(Raj:)She never even got
to see my penis.
(Raj:)Ta-da!
(Priya:)Who wants some
more coffee?